Finding Aid for the National Hispanic Media Coalition Subject Files PASC.0278
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Ralph Segura - correspondence with NHMC about National Hispanic Media name and The Milagro Beanfield, (1987-1988, 1990) (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Ramar Communications - application to acquire KIDI (Albuquerque, NM), (1991 Nov 6) (Box 32, Folder 10)
  FCC form 314
- Ray Blanco - letter to Alex Nogales, (2000 Feb 15) (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Reed Hundt, (1994-1996) (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Reforma - newsletter and mailing list, (1997-1998) (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Regal Biltmore Hotel 1999 - confirmation letter - Impact Awards gala, (1999 Feb 17) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  Regal Biltmore Hotel "1999" - accommodation confirmation letter for Impact Awards gala.
- Renewal application for insurance from Executive Risk Indemnity, (1999 Jan 30) (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Research (1 of 2) - photocopies of articles and/or book chapters related to minorities in the media, (1988) (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Research (2 of 2) - photocopies of articles and/or book chapters related to minorities in the media, (1988) (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Resumes - Javier Navarro and Thomas Baiz, (no date) (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Rey Hernandez - interview in Shooter World publication, (1996) (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Robert Iger - Broadcasting and Cable clipping, (1994 Oct 31) (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Roberto Rodriguez and Patrisia Gonzales - Latino Spectrum column, (1994 Feb - March) (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Rockwell - NHMC funding request for 10th anniversary banquet, (1996 Sept 24) (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Rocky Mountain News - boycott by the People's Coalition for Responsible Media, (1982-1987) (Box 29, Folder 4)
- SAG (Screen Actors Guild) - dispute over Hispanic Film Project - Tanto Tiempo and Always Roses, (1997-1999) (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Sale of transfer of control to Hallmark - FCC filings and petitions, cover letters and clippings, (1987) (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Sally Martinez - correspondence for Henry Cisneros reception, (1997) (Box 9, Folder 17)
- San Diego [NHMC] Chapter - clipping and meeting/retreat information, (1998-1999) (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Santiago Pozo - Arenas Group information, (1995 May) (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Santo Bugito - thank you letter to NHMC, (1996 Jan 22) (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Satellite TV - clipping, (no date) (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Scholarships - request for NHMC to identify possible candidates, (1996) (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Scott Ealy - position paper titled: Racial Discrimination in Broadcast Radio Programming: It Remains Violative of the FCC's 'Public Interest' Standard, (1995 Aug 2) (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Screen Actors Guild (SAG) - Jerry Velasco and Miluka Rivera complaint against Richard Yniguez, (1995 Feb - May) (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Seed Chapter Grant [NHMC] - Letters of Agreement from San Diego, San Antonio, Tucson, and New York, (1998 Nov 21) (Box 17, Folder 16)
- SHPE (Society of Hispanic Engineers) - conference information, (1997 March) (Box 16, Folder 6)
- SHPE (Society of Hispanic Professional Engineers) - Hispanic Engineer Magazine, (1987 Fall) (Box 23, Folder 1)
- SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation)/Hallmark - correspondence re: opposition to acquisition, (1986 Aug -1987) (Box 36, Folder 9)
- SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation)/Hallmark - declarations of P. Bohmer and N. Leventhal, (1986 Sept) (Box 36, Folder 7)
- SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation)/Hallmark - press releases, handwritten notes, research, (1986) (Box 37, Folder 3)
- SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation)/Hallmark - related FCC documents, (1986) (Box 36, Folder 8)
- SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation)/Hallmark - related FCC documents - reply memo of TVL re: motion to intervene, (1986 Sept) (Box 36, Folder 5)
  With declarations by R. Tapia, D. Lizarraga, G. Loving, J. Riley, V. Curtis, D. Asencio, J. Whitman, and E. Torres.
- SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation)/Hallmark - related FCC documents In the Application for Transfer of Control and Renewal Licenses, (1987) (Box 36, Folder 4)
- SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation)/Hallmark - research, (no date) (Box 36, Folder 6)
- SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation)/Mass Media Bureau - joint opposition FCC filing - petition to intervene proposed settlement, (1986 Sept) (Box 37, Folder 1)
  Petitioners include MABA (Mexican American Bar Association of Los Angeles County), LULAC (League of United Latin American Citizens), MAPA (Mexican American Political Association), LACCEA (Los Angeles County Chicano Employee Association) and MAGA (Mexican American Grocers Association).
- SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation)/Mass Media Bureau - joint opposition FCC filing - application for review, (1986 Oct) (Box 37, Folder 2)
  Petitioners include MABA (Mexican American Bar Association of Los Angeles County), (League of United Latin American Citizens), MAPA (Mexican American Political Association), LACCEA (Los Angeles County Chicano Employee Association) and MAGA (Mexican American Grocers Association).
- SiTV - comedians list and Ana Nogales co-host possibilities, (1998 July 8) (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Solomon Ortiz - press releases and clippings, (1994-1997) (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Includes his activities with the US Congressional Hispanic Caucus Task Force on Arts and Entertainment, e.g., ABC/Disney.
- Sonny Skyhawk - fax to NHMC for support, (1997 Aug 18) (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Southern Christian Leadership Conference - Minorities in the Media meeting summary, (1989 Aug 23) (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Southwest Regional Community Education Services - presentation titled: TV Viewing Skills Workshop, (no date) (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Spanish Pornography - article draft for La Opinion by Dr. Gabriel Aguilar, (1995 Nov 7) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Spanish.
- Station meetings to All Board members - memo, (1999 Feb 10) (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Statistics [FCC] - broadcast station licensed as of Jan. 31, 1999, (1999 Jan) (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Steve Figueroa - Victor Valley clipping, (1996 Dec 10) (Box 14, Folder 24)
- StreetLights Production Assistant program - information packet, (1996-1998) (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Studios - list LA area movie studios from unidentified publication, (1997 March 26) (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Su Familia - press release and 1999 winter edition, (1999 Feb) (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Sue Welsh (1 of 2) - Impact Awards Gala files, (1997) (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Sue Welsh (2 of 2) - Impact Awards Gala files, (1997) (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Summer Fundraiser 95 - thank you letters to financial contributors, planning information, (ca. 1994-1995) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Support nominations - letters from NHMC supporting Fred Martel and Diana Bonta, (1999 Jan 28) (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Susana Arellano - LA Times boycott, (1998) (Box 16, Folder 2)
- T.V. - clippings, (1996-1997) (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Talk Shows - Monitor American Psychological Association clipping, (1997 Aug) (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Tardeada 97 - fundraiser planning materials, (1997) (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Tardeada 99 - financial pledges, (1999) (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Tardeada hotel information - accommodations for unidentified events, (1998-1999) (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Taxes - [NHMC] Returns, (1993-1994) (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Ted Harbert - LA Times clipping, (1997 Jan 8) (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Ted Turner - Daily Variety clipping, (1995 Nov 30) (Box 5, Folder 13)
- TELACU (The East Los Angeles Community Union) - scholarship award invite to Alex Nogales, (1996 Oct 7) (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Telecomm Bill - clippings, (ca. 1995) (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Telecommunications Act 1996 - FCC Notice of Inquiry, (1996 May 21) (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Telemundo - Annual reports, (1988) (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Telemundo - Latino community concerns, (1989-1990) (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Telemundo - partnership agreement with NHMC, (1994-1997) (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Telephone - Public Utilities Commission clipping, (1995 July 24) (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Television V-Chip - LA Times clipping, (1996 Dec 20) (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Terry Crofoot - Daily Variety clipping, (1996 April 10) (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Texaco discrimination - LA Times clipping, (1996 Nov 13) (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Texas Music Awards - Texas Talent Musicians Association complaint against Howard Stern, (ca. 1995) (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Thank you letters (7/18) - Washington DC (Hill), (1987) (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Theresa Brown - invitation to speak at CA State University, Northridge, (1997 March 18) (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Times Mirror - annual reports, (1986-1987) (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Tomas - Mostly Eclectic Radio, (1995 April) (Box 31, Folder 12)
  With Alex Nogales interview tape. File may have been created by Alex Nogales.
- Tomas Rivera Center - invitation letter to Alex Nogalesfor service on committee for study titled Building the On-Ramps to the Information Superhighway: The State of Educational Technology in Eastern Los Angeles Schools, (1995 May 15) (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Tomas Rivera Policy Institute - Sept 1998 report: Talking Back to TV: Latinos Discuss How Television Portrays Them and the Quality of Programming Options, (1999 May 7) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  With letter from E.R. to Dr. Pachon about NHMC retreat
- Tony Plana - Santo Bugito, (1995-1996) (Box 31, Folder 19)
  With script titled: The Latino Family Project. File may have been created by Alex Nogales.
- Tribune Company - annual report, (1988) (Box 25, Folder 20)
- TTMA (Texas Talent Musicians Association) - XVI Annual Tejano Music Awards press kit, (1996) (Box 9, Folder 24)
- TV Family Hour - LA Times clipping, (1996 Dec 12) (Box 9, Folder 25)
- TV Power Players '96 - clippings, (ca. 1996) (Box 9, Folder 4)
- TV stations maps - Los Angeles, (no date) (Box 16, Folder 19)
- TV stations percentage of Hispanic employees in NY and LA, (1994) (Box 25, Folder 10)
- TV Studies - Wall Street Journal clipping, (1996 Nov 6) (Box 9, Folder 27)
- TV Week - clipping, (1993 Aug 8-14) (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Twenty Years After the Kerner Report: Media Coverage of Race Relations published by the New California Alliance, (1988 Sept 30) (Box 30, Folder 2)
- UCLA Center for Communication Policy - invite for Alex Nogalesto write an article, (1997 April 2) (Box 12, Folder 27)
  letter inviting A.N. to write an article
- ULPA (United Latino Political Association) - announcement - General elections candidates forum, (1990) (Box 38, Folder 8)
- United Farm Workers - press release, (1998 June) (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Unity 94 conference, Atlanta, GA - speaker notes and program, (1994 July) (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Unity Project - News Watch: A Critical Look at Coverage of People of Color publication, (1994) (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Universal 93 project - notes, (1993,1997) (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Universal meeting, (1995 July) (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Universal Tours recruitment - job announcements and NHMC form letters, (1987 Nov - 1988 Jan) (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Universal/MCA - communications re: employment advocacy and the Milagro Bean Field project, (1987-1989) (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Univision - children's programming, (1994-1998) (Box 31, Folder 3)
  With clippings and communications about other topics. File may have been created by Alex Nogales.
- Univision - NHMC's FCC petition to deny transfer of ownership, (1992) (Box 30, Folder 7)
  With research by HIPFT (Hispanic Independent Producers for Television) and EIR (Executive Intelligence Review).
- Univision - NHMC's filings with US Court of Appeals, (1992-1993) (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Univision - Ray Rodriguez address to the National Hispanic Corporate Council, (1992 July 16) (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Univision (1 of 2) - FCC related documents and clippings, (1992-1994) (Box 32, Folder 8)
  Submitted by Univision, NHMC, LULAC and others. May include duplicate documents found in Univision related files.
- Univision (2 of 2) - FCC related documents and clippings, (1992-1994) (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Univision (Station K48AM) Albuquerque, New Mexico - NHMC's FCC petition to deny renewal application, (1992-1993) (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Univision [FCC] applications, (1992) (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Univision Albuquerque Station license application and renewal of license [1 of 3], (1992-1994) (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Univision Albuquerque Station license application and renewal of license [2 of 3], (1992-1994) (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Univision Albuquerque Station license application and renewal of license [3 of 3], (1992-1994) (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Univision American GI Forum petition for denial, (1992 June-Aug) (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Univision Cahill meeting, (1992) (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Univision Court of Appeals, (1994) (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Univision El Juez - press kit, (1989 April 17) (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Univision Exemption - FCC syndication, financial interest and primetime access rules, (1989) (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Univision network agreement [incomplete], (1992 April) (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Univision Sale, (1992) (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Univision sale to J. Perenchio, E. Azcarraga, Grupo Cisneros (1of 2) - oppositional research, (1992) (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Univision sale to J. Perenchio, E. Azcarraga, Grupo Cisneros (2 of 2) - oppositional research, (1992) (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Univision stock purchase agreement, (1992-1993) (Box 30, Folder 11)
  With FCC filings.
- Univision Stock Purchase Agreement, (1992 April 8) (Box 32, Folder 5)
  Agreement between Sunshine Acquisition, Corporacion Venezolana de Television, Hallmark Cards and Univision.
- Univision/Hallmark - Bermuda Trust Co. Limited request for declaratory ruling, (1988 July) (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Univision/Hallmark (1 of 2) - related FCC applications involving Bahia de San Francisco, SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation), and SALAD (Spanish American League Against Discrimination), (1987-1988) (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Univision/Hallmark (1 of 4) - related FCC documents in application of SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation), (1986) (Box 35, Folder 6)
  With chronological index of documents.
- Univision/Hallmark (1 of 5) - FCC filings and US Court of Appeals documents in the matter of SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation), (1985-1986) (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Univision/Hallmark (2 of 2) - related FCC applications involving Bahia de San Francisco, SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation), and SALAD (Spanish American League Against Discrimination), (1987-1988) (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Univision/Hallmark (2 of 4) - related FCC documents in application of SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation), (1986) (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Univision/Hallmark (2 of 5) - FCC filings and US Court of Appeals documents in the matter of SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation), (1985-1986) (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Univision/Hallmark (3 of 4) - related FCC documents in application of SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation), (1986) (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Univision/Hallmark (3 of 5) - FCC filings and US Court of Appeals documents in the matter of SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation), (1985-1986) (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Univision/Hallmark (4 of 4) - related FCC documents in application of SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation), (1986-1987) (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Univision/Hallmark (4 of 5) - FCC filings and US Court of Appeals documents in the matter of SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation), (1985-1986) (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Univision/Hallmark (5 of 5) - FCC filings and US Court of Appeals documents in the matter of SICC (Spanish International Communications Corporation), (1985-1986) (Box 35, Folder 5)
- US citizenship - La Opinion clippings, (1997 Sept 12-13) (Box 15, Folder 15)
- US Citizenship Action Network - Citizenship Day event information, (1997 Aug-Sept) (Box 15, Folder 16)
- US Commission on Civil Rights - press release, (1994 Oct 19) (Box 19, Folder 21)
- US Department of Commerce News - press releases, (1987, 1989) (Box 25, Folder 21)
- USC (Hispanic Directory) of LA - update request, (1996) (Box 9, Folder 28)
- USHCC (U.S. Hispanic Chamber of Commerce) - newsletter, (1995 Dec) (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Valle, Carmen del - snapshot, (no date) (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Victims of a Crime - agenda, (1997 Feb 5) (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Victoria Castro (LAUSD Board member) - complaint against Disney/ABC, (1997 March-May) (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Video games - LA Times clipping, (1996 Dec 6) (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Video sales - LA Times clipping, (1997 April 30) (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Viva America - proposal for television, (1990 July) (Box 27, Folder 12)
- WABC TV - NHMC's FCC comments about license renewal, (1994 May 2) (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Walt Disney Co. - annual report, (1996) (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Walter Liss - Daily Variety clipping, (1996 Oct 24) (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Washington DC - FCC informational material and letters - 1987 FCC acts and House bills (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Washington DC meeting - July 16-19 meeting materials, (1987 July) (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Washington meeting and outreach - NHMC meetings, (1987) (Box 29, Folder 5)
- WATL (TV) - Rainbow's FCC petition to deny renewal license, (1993 March 19) (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Watts/Century Latino organization - 7th annual celebration invite, (1998 April 6) (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Wayne Rickert - NBC organizational charts, (1996) (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Welfare Reform Law - informational material, (1996) (Box 9, Folder 33)
- WGA (Writers Guild of America) - Latino writers list, (no date) (Box 9, Folder 35)
- WGBS-TV - supplement to petition to deny filed by NAACP, (1993 Nov 19) (Box 19, Folder 23)
- White House Fellowships - information packet, (1996) (Box 9, Folder 34)
- WJQX (FM) - NHMC's FCC petition to revoke license, (1995) (Box 19, Folder 24)
  With WJQX's FCC response to NHMC's petition and NHMC's reply to WJQX.
- WNYW-TV - FCC Renewal application - supplement to petition to deny, (1995 Jan) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  Fox misconduct in connection with Gingrich book deal.
- Wood, Lucksinger, Epstein (Thompson, Kramer) - attorney correspondence - KCBS Hispanic employment, (1987-1988) (Box 22, Folder 5)
- WPIX FCC Renewal application - response to NHMC and NPRF (National Puerto Rican Forum) comments, (1989 May) (Box 25, Folder 22)
- WWOR TV - NHMC's FCC petition to deny license renewal, (1994 April - May) (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Xavier Beccera - congressional Hispanic caucus, (1997 April, June) (Box 15, Folder 20)